obsessable.com 2010-11-22

# Privacy Policy

**Introduction and Scope**

In this Privacy Policy, we (Crowd Fusion, Inc. and its wholly owned properties) describe how we use personally identifiable information about you that we collect through webpages at [www.crowdfusion.com](http://crowdfusion.com/), [www.obsessable.com](http://obsessable.com/) and others that display a direct link to this Privacy Policy (each a "Site" and together the "Sites"). This Privacy Policy does not apply to any other data, including, without limitation, data that we collect offline or data that others collect on websites that are linked to the Sites.

The Sites are not intended for children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information via the Sites from visitors in any age group. We do, however, collect information under specific circumstances.

You actively send information to us when you sign up with us a member on a Site, participate in surveys or promotions, post opinions on our bulletin boards, respond to us or otherwise contact us. Depending on your choices, you may send us personally identifiable information such as your email address, name, mailing address, phone number, birthday, and gender; password. But, you can also use certain features of our Sites without telling us your name and if you do not tell us who you are, we do not try to find out.

We also track information about how our Site is used by you through cookies, Internet tags or web beacons, and navigational data collection (log files, server logs, clickstream — or other methods). For example, your Internet browser automatically transmits to us information such as the URL of the website you just came from and the Internet Protocol (IP) address and the browser version your computer is currently using.

To accomplish some of the foregoing data processing, we utilize independent contractors. Click here to read about examples of some of our contractors and how we work with them.

In addition, we participate in ad networks. The ad networks that we participate in collect anonymous information using cookies to target some of the advertising you see on the Sites and on other third party websites. Each of these ad networks in which Crowd Fusion participates has their own advertising and privacy policies.

You can set your browser to notify you when a cookie is sent or to refuse or delete cookies altogether, but certain features of the Sites might not work without certain cookies.

If you have actively sent us your name or other personally identifiable information, we may combine such information with tracked information for the purposes set forth below.

**Disclosure of Data**

We keep your personally identifiable information confidential and we generally do not disclose it. But, please note the following clarifications and exceptions:

If we ever sell a Site or substantial parts of our business, we may disclose your personally identifiable information to a (prospective) buyer on the condition that such buyer agrees to comply with this Privacy Policy.

We may also share your personally identifiable information to respond to law enforcement requests, court orders or other legal process or if we believe that such disclosure is necessary to investigate, prevent or respond to illegal activities, fraud, physical threats to you or others or as otherwise required by any applicable law or regulation. Even though we do not provide any personally identifiable information about you specifically to any advertising customers, they can occasionally find out information indirectly.

Before we disclose your personally identifiable data to a third party for their own business purposes (such as a survey or a sweepstake), we will first obtain your consent, for example via email, click-through, an online opportunity to opt-out or otherwise. Our employees and independent contractors may have access to some of your personally identifiable information for the purpose of helping us run our business (and not for their own purposes). They access and use such data subject to our instructions, on a "need to know" basis and under confidentiality and security obligations.

We freely use and disclose data in anonymous form, for example, in statistics or reports to our advertising customers.

Please remember that if you post any information in areas of our Sites that are generally accessible to users, such as chat rooms and message boards, it will be available to the public.

**Security**

We take reasonable steps to protect personally identifiable information from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. But, you should keep in mind that no Internet transmission is ever completely secure or error-free. In particular, e-mail sent to or from the Sites may not be secure.

If you have any questions, comments or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us via email at [privacy at crowd fusion dot com](http://tinyurl.com/cf-privacy-email).

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy is effective September 24th, 2008. We reserve the right to amend it from time to time and if we change it materially, we will post a revised version on the Sites. Please check back periodically, and especially before you provide any personally identifiable information to us.

**Terms of Use**

Note also that your use of the Sites is subject to our Terms of Use, which contain disclaimers, limitations of liability and a choice of California or New York law.
